Howdy.
Hey, Gary.
How are you doing?
Today?
Yeah.
In fact, it's my birthday.
Is it?
Happy birthday, Gary.
I didn't know.
Wow.
So nice to have this overlap with that.
Yeah, very nice.
I see you play guitar.
I see the guitar in the background.
Yeah.
Do you play on a regular basis or have you haven't touched it in a while?
I had my guitar instructor this morning.
Yes.
I don't do as much practice as I ought to, but I am making some progress.
Yeah.
I have a few guitars myself, but I haven't touched them in a very long time.
Oh, auvre pour guitar.
Guitar cell.
You've been classical.
Right.
Nice.
But what I've been learning is Final Fantasy songs.
Oh.
Awesome.
Which songs?
Easy.
All Nabu Alamatsu songs or what?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, that was the heyday of Final Fantasy music.
Hey, Wade.
Hey, Dick.
Morning.
Pretty good.
I
think Gary wants to switch over to a bottom.
Yeah, I'm the bar.
But Delfina has been performing recently.
Yeah, Delfina has not just been performing recently.
She has been, you know, the balancing between Vukredin's, you know, the double Vs.
Maybe that's the new band.
Yeah, pretty cool.
Hold on, Gary.
Yeah, learning finger-picking technique as well.
It's not the easiest one.
Well, you know, I have the nails for it.
It's been a minute.
Did you change your hair, Staris?
No, I just woke up.
Me too.
It's like nine o'clock at night, dude.
And I took a nap.
So how's Belgium?
Well, Belgium's fun.
Going from, I went, I was in California.
I went to India.
I went back to California and I went to Belgium.
But I'm actually not in Belgium right now.
Right now I'm in Luxembourg.
Yesterday, I was in Belgium, Holland, and Luxembourg.
Nice.
Europe is small.
Sort of.
I saw a silly one.
What was it?
You could drive like, I don't know, 28 hours or something and still be in Greece or something because you were going around the landmass and hitting the northern tip of Africa or whatever.
Yeah.
So yes, it was definitely fun.
I enjoyed the food.
After a week in India, I'm enjoying eating meat.
Yes.
And so, yes, I am enjoying that.
But I have not had good beer yet.
This is a big disappointment.
Yeah, I found good beer in Belgium and Luxembourg.
Really?
No, no.
I mean...
Get that man a bud light.
I've had good wine.
I've had good food, but like there's, you know, my Belgian hosts are like, no, no, no, you cannot have beer here.
You must have beer over there.
Okay.
They're big snobs about where you drink your beer.
Yes, yes.
No.
Well, it was easy to get good beer in Zurich and Munich.
Oh, yeah.
Like the thing with Belgians is they take getting good beer to the next level.
So I was able to drink beer, but like, you know, special moments in special places.
Maybe I can have the right beer.
Right.
Like, they've got like 280.
They got some like ridiculous number of specialized beers that are very good.
Yeah.
So anyway, the most important thing is I'm here.
I can get logged into my role 20.
Hopefully.
Maybe.
Joker.
So I heard that we decided to be poor hosts, poor house guests.
We?
No, actually, to be strictly accurate, you were not poor house guests.
We're very rich house guests.
Because you were asleep during all of this.
You were asleep during all of this.
Valfine woke up to discover that the cult of Talos was very poor guests.
Oh, my goodness.
Right, Dave, did you tell Valfina that you spent the evening?
No, did you?
I can't remember.
I read some summaries, but Valfina actually doesn't know.
Valfina was sleeping during all, as was Brewberry.
And so they woke up in the morning and the bard, sorry, the Falcon Hunter accused the cult of Talos of hunting for his special ring.
Okay.
The Sulcradian did not actually steal anything.
He left it all back where it is because, you know, he's not a thief.
What are the cults of Talos doing here?
Like, what are their goals?
Well, so the cult of Talos is tied to lightning.
Talos is a lightning god.
And the lighthouse that we were at?
That was, you know, cult of Talos.
And there's also the orcs at the Wooden Mance that are tied to Talos.
And then there's the fact that there's all these orcs have been a little bit more organized.
And then whether that's about the carvers behind that or the shamans of the cult of Talos are behind that is still uncertain.
And what is this about Imrith?
Really?
Imrith?
Well, you know, Imrith was a famous, wasn't just some random dragon.
She was known as the Doom of the Desert.
And, you know, when she, the Falcon Hunter's story, I mean, you know, it's a story, right?
Is that, you know, the love of his life was killed and he wanted to go get his revenge.
He shows up after the Doom of the Desert's dead.
And, you know, he goes through all the treasure, but there was none left because it had been picked clean.
But there was a few pieces left, and one of them was this magic ring.
This ring.
Imrith was killed?
Well, I mean, that's the version of the story he knew.
Okay.
All right.
You know, he heard Imrith was defeated, you know, but when he arrived there, he found lots of cadavers of giants, you know.
No dragon cadaver, but what do you know, right?
Well, maybe it was one of her experiments.
Yeah, who knows?
Who knows?
But yeah, so just so yeah, so that that's the that's the version of the events that you that that were presented to you.
The exact circumstances of Imrit's disappearance, death, whatever are hotly contested among the sages, as we said.
Some people have said it was because of Orsic and his heroism.
Others have, of course, said, you know, it was all managed by the seer who was, you know, others have blamed it on other factions, but you know, who knows?
Who knows?
The point of the matter is the Falcon Hunter found some spare gold, used the spare gold to buy this house, use that house his claims of stealing a dragon horde.
And, you know, strictly speaking, you know, he defeated a dragon and got a dragon horde as a way to buff up his reputation to get tourists to visit the Falcon Hunter Lodge.
All right, then.
Yes.
I mean, you know.
Sounds like you should keep a good eye on that cult of the Talos.
Yes, yes.
And, you know, Dave, did you, and I also think you got some conflict-free gold as a result of all of this, if I recall correctly?
Or no, you did not.
I've never had to play the game of Dungeons and Dragons where conflict-free gold.
An interesting concept, yes.
Yes.
That is definitely one of the more novel and interesting ideas.
Okay, so were we going to leave?
You were leaving.
Yeah, you're headed towards the logger's camp.
Okay.
So, this is through Never Winterwood, right?
Yep, yep, yep.
We saw it in the lodge map.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm just my number one contribution.
Yes.
Kelly Coast taught us where we're at.
It's an important contribution because Cassada is sometimes just confused.
The tools are wonky.
All right.
Okay, so the fellow.
All right, so yes.
Okay, so off we are to the thing.
All right.
You should see the map of the North Sword Coast.
And you were at the Falcon Hunting Lodge.
And so now I presume you're going to go through the Never Winter Wood to the Logger's Camp.
All right.
And
you guys are third level, right?
I think so.
Good question.
Have level three.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's right.
It was like you'd forgotten to give us level two at some point.
So we like double leveled once.
Yes.
Or like back-to-back or something.
Anyway.
All right.
As you are marching through the forest, I presume you're trying to be somewhat discreet and not, you know.
Well, as much as a Goliath barbarian can be discreet, yes.
He just said not discreet at all.
Singing at the top of your forest, at the top of your lungs.
There's no shame.
All right.
We'll use this map.
No?
See, hold on.
I need a map.
And so they've.
What prompted you to do this cover operation at the Falcon Secret?
Is it just curiosity?
No, it was the goal was to, you know, I was, I think, offended at him and his building his lodge on the backs of treasure that he that was, you know, stolen property and that I am not a thief, not going to steal it back.
I want to show him the error of his ways.
And I was looking for information on the sort of the rightful owners of the so-called treasure so that we could perhaps track those people down and list them in helping him understand what he has stolen.
A persuasion can be.
Right.
So what do you make of what you found at the lodge?
Well, we're going to need more information.
I mean, we got a description of the ring and we know what's written on it and so on, but we'll need to take that information back to, for example, Sir Karen and list him.
See if he has any thoughts on what it all might mean.
Right now, there wasn't like a piece of paper that said, you know, owned by this person.
So some investigation will be necessary.
So something strikes me as funny is that you said you wanted to show him the error of his ways and yet you deceived him when it was time to confront him and let him believe that it was not steal anything.
Well, the full stantry is still not very nice, isn't it?
Yeah, but he's wrong.
Okay, so that makes you right then.
Or Century is just normal.
I see.
Dodgy morals used to power.
I think I have much better morals than most of the people in this campaign that we've encountered.
Yeah, well, I mean, like, for Century, I mean, Mike Mate's right.
I mean, that's the way the cities are run, right?
I see.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I'm glad you did it and found the information that you found.
It's just that it seems a bit out of character for you.
All right.
I'm looking forward to the conversation with Imrith, though, when we find her.
And you give her back the ring and say, hey, somebody took this from you.
Here it is.
She is not the rightful owner of the ring.
Are you kidding me?
She stole it, too.
Oh, I see.
It goes that far back, huh?
You know, to be fair, everybody.
Okay.
Who's leading this merry band of pirates?
Well, it's got to be me, the tallest one, walking, right?
Blueberry in the lead.
Yes.
Okay, the blueberry.
The new Ark, is anybody standing next to him, or are you choosing to be constrained by his passive perception?
Just asking.
I'll be in the front too.
Okay.
I was just curious.
I wasn't trying to hint that anything is about to happen.
I don't want anybody to be under that impression.
Passive perception.
I rolled my perception.
What is your passive perception, by the way?
15.
But I rolled my perception.
10.
All right.
There it is.
Okay.
I'm not bothering to roll mine.
I've got minus one and ten as passive.
All right.
Nine as passive perception.
Aaron, Soma, and all right.
So as you are
tokens, all right.
And Barry.
That's what I'm assuming.
Right.
Okay.
So as you guys are marching, you notice orc scout just ahead.
I'm just going to change the map to get to the right.
Alright.
So this is.
Ah, you've got the map there.
Good.
Check.
I just was trying to get the map set up.
All right.
So you notice an orc scout up ahead.
Okay, what is he doing?
I mean, is he trying to conceal himself?
Yes, he's like trying to.
He is trying to conceal himself, sort of like trying to see what's up ahead.
Like, you know, he's roll your insight.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yes.
I mean, to the best of your knowledge, you think he's just like taking a look around to look-see.
He's, you know.
Wait, maybe I get to double that.
I think I get to double that, don't I?
Because of the staff.
I'm going to double-check what that was.
He's just orcing it up.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys are looking that way.
Is he looking for you or is he looking for food?
It's kind of hard to tell.
Right.
Has he noticed that we noticed that?
Soma figures out that Soma scratches her shell for a moment and realizes that all of you wet behind the shell types don't realize that this orc is on the lookout for some kind of group that's probably trying to set up an ambush a little bit further up.
Sorry.
I remember I have advantage on wisdom in nature or in boards, whatever.
All right.
He hasn't quite noticed you yet.
Orcs make good slaves.
He hasn't noticed us, but we noticed him, and we think it's going to be an ambush.
He's a lookout who's a very, very poor lookout.
Yeah.
Definitely.
So let's see.
What should we do, guys?
I mean, creep up as an animal.
Maybe you wouldn't notice that.
That's a good plan.
I'm going to have to stay behind then.
Hold on.
Do I have wolf?
I forget where it is.
We could hide in the woods.
Well, just to be clear, you also have a cart with you, right?
Oh, that's right.
With my wine.
No way they're getting that.
I mean, yes, they do have.
They are threatening your wine, just I thought you should know that.
All right.
I mean, over my dead buddy, for sure.
I mean, my suggestion is, you know, casually walk up as a bear, you know, shitting in the woods.
All right.
Let's see.
I should be able to do this.
But be on the ready, since we're aware there's going to be an ambush here.
Yes.
Where is.
There we go.
I mean, yeah, I assume that, like.
So, I mean, I'm not out of place, right?
Like, I'm just, I'm part of the wild.
You're just a bear.
A bear is like a totally normal thing.
It's not like anybody's expecting, you know, a bear.
All right.
Let's say I just, you know, cross most of the distance and, you know, obviously we spot each other, right?
Yes.
What happens if I roar at him?
Ooh, you roar at him.
I do.
Okay, now I have to think what he does.
There you go.
In your bear shape, can't you smell how many others they are?
I don't think bear has any particular.
In fact, my passive perception is only 13 in bear shape.
I mean, we can give it a shot.
You know the saying, right?
When there's a pine needle drops in the forest, the deer can hear it, and then the bear can smell it.
All right, what did you roll?
Not high.
12.
13 minus 1.
I don't even.
Can I at least get a direction?
No, you don't pick up anything.
All right.
How's he react to the roar?
He.
What he does is he quickly scrambles up a tree and sort of makes hand motions to the rear to the rear the north to the north.
Okay, this way.
All right.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Do you move forward or do you stay where you are?
I mean, I make a token attack at the tree, right?
Like, just try to shake him loose.
All right.
I'm going to slip in the woods while all of this is happening.
Okay.
So why don't we roll for initiative?
We're doing that already.
All right.
No, I mean, it depends like sequencing of things is going to matter.
Yeah, I get you.
I get you.
Oh, damn it.
This thing keeps popping up.
How do I turn off this turn order?
I'll fix it.
Oh, it's you putting it in.
All right.
It's me.
Let me turn that off.
All right.
I need to just
put myself in the corner of the whole map because I don't exist.
And my actual health is supposed to be 36.
Okay.
All right.
I need one more thing to do.
There we go.
36 out of 27.
I don't know how I feel about the bonus HP changes, but whatever.
You don't know?
I don't know.
They're different.
I mean, there's good and bad.
I got used to dealing with druids in a different way.
Okay.
All right.
Let me see what his initiative would be.
Initiative is just one.
All right.
Can someone sort?
Hold on, let me just sort.
All right.
ZJ.
All right, Vukridin, you're up.
You're staying behind, I presume.
Yeah, I'm not doing anything.
All right.
Brewberry, are you advancing?
Yes, I'm trying to sneak through the woods as much as I can.
Just switch direction.
Somewhere over here, I suppose.
All right.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
So you're pulling the cart with you.
No, leave the cart.
Leave the cart.
Cart will be fine.
He's not going to be separated from his wine.
Is the cart moving or not?
No.
It's not.
Is that what I heard?
No.
It's not moving.
All right.
So the cart does not move.
The cart stays there.
Brewberry, you're trying to move stealthily, right?
I'm trying to, yes.
Roll your stealth.
Oh, God.
Do you have disadvantage on stealth?
It's not too bad.
You don't have disadvantage.
Do you have medium armor?
I believe he does.
Yeah, you have disadvantage.
Uh-oh.
Why is this not rolling?
How does this stupid pop-up?
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, let's scale me.
All right.
11.
It's not super stealthy.
All right.
So.
Okay.
You do not see the orc, but the orc sees you.
We've already.
Oh, am I the only one who actually saw the scout?
No, because there's another orc.
Oh.
Not that orc.
No, no.
There is another orc.
There is another.
All right.
So this other orc sees you, and he decides to shout to his friends.
Okay, so there's more orcs, yeah.
Yes.
And so, Soma.
There's a moving rock.
Does anybody here speak orc?
Yes, I speak orc.
Yeah, what he says, he starts screaming at the scout saying, you are the blah, blah, blah of a useless turd, and I should never have taken you.
And like, why did I get stuck with you of all the orcs of all the scouts?
And like, you were distracted by a damn bear.
The damn bear.
Speaking of.
Speaking of, all right.
So let me just roll for these are a few more orc types.
How high up in the tree did this guy climb?
I'd say taller than not so high that it's super high, but high enough that you can't reach him.
How about I leave it at that?
So what's your tight?
Seven feet?
So let's say 10 feet?
It's pretty tall.
Yeah.
I mean, I have a 30-foot climb.
I know.
He didn't quite think through this whole thing.
No, he's bear chow.
Just to be clear, he did not think through the implications.
See, previous comment that you the dumbest scout in the world.
Yeah, he's like, the dumbest scout in the world.
Like, and like, you know, what the hell?
And I'm sort of like done with you and your mother.
And I didn't really, this was not my choice.
And if it had been up to me, blah, blah, blah.
Hold on.
I need to.
Sorry, I'm on my laptop and I don't have my 26-inch screen.
Size queen.
What?
Yeah, size queen.
Yeah, I'm very much a size queen.
And I'm struggling with like my monitors, right?
And my Windows because like, how the hell did, how do I help?
How do people, how did people function back when they only had a few monitors?
Could you tell me that?
Alt tab.
What?
Oh, alt-tab.
Yes.
Forgot about that.
Okay.
I think you can do Windows tab as well if you're on Windows.
Don't do that.
The Windows tab is so obnoxious.
Depends on what information you're looking for.
I suppose.
I don't have that many windows open at a time.
All right.
I just need to write it down.
I'm just not sure I got there.
All right.
Can you guys see the names orc writer?
No.
All right.
Nope.
Can you now see it?
Oh, hold on.
My window seems to have frozen.
Let me refresh.
Orc Raider 1, Orc Raider 2.
Okay, good.
So you can see it.
And the other one is Orc Brigand.
All right, cool.
The last guy is Orc Scout, but I will.
He won't be here for long.
All right.
Okay.
He starts screaming about his mother, and you know, blah, blah, blah.
And the Orc Scout shouts, What do you mean?
And, you know, right.
Yeah.
I climbed the tree.
All right.
Hold on.
Valfine.
Okay.
So, so you're up, yes.
Yeah, I climb the tree.
You climb the tree.
All right.
Now, climb at 30 feet.
This is cake for a bear.
All right.
Yeah, let's see if we can't knock him down.
Are you going to shove?
So, are you going to shove it?
I'm just going to bonk him.
Okay, just one task.
What the heck just happened in my roll 20?
Give me a click and drive.
What the heck?
Yeah, I had to refresh the page.
What on earth is this?
Make sure to steal the honey when you're up there.
I think I missed.
I don't understand what the heck's going on.
Sorry, it's like the whole like it made me roll die on the roll 20 instead of the DD Beyond.
All right.
Well, that's the first attack.
Second attack will go.
I did claws first, right?
Yes.
There we go.
That's a hit.
Yeah, that's it.
You take a bite out of him, I presume.
Looks like only eight damage.
Yep.
I updated the hit points.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Okay, I guess I'm up in the tree.
You're up in the tree.
All right.
Who is next?
Valfine.
No, Scout.
The Scout gets to the point.
Oh, yeah, right, right, right.
Sorry.
I had planned on doing some more damage.
So, where do you see the older of the encounter?
Although the round.
Let me drop that in Discord.
You just did a spreadsheet.
Yes.
Ah, okay.
Oh, you have it.
Yes, I have it.
We use that spreadsheet.
All right.
Okay.
It allows us to keep track of conditions and stats more than everything.
Yeah, and everything's in there, like our quest items, our quests themselves, things like that.
All right, cool.
What does the scout do?
Let me see.
What can he do?
All right.
The first thing he does is he disengages.
Coward.
Two, three.
All right.
And then after he disengages, he aims his arrow at you.
At you being the bear.
The bear just attacked him, right?
He has two actions.
Yeah, he has a disengage and a move and a shoot.
It's a dead bonus action.
He has disengages a bonus action.
He's a rogue, I guess.
Isn't that pretty standard?
And he uses his longbow.
No, it is not, Wade.
All right.
It is not.
He uses his longbow to attack the bear.
Roll the 17 and I do nine points of damage.
Aw, that takes me down to my normal hit points.
Okay.
Who's up next?
I think it's me.
All right.
Valfine?
Yeah.
Who can I see?
You'll have to move to see somebody, I think, from where you are.
And I know that the scout is there, but I don't know about anyone else.
So let me see this.
It depends.
Like, you have partial.
You can see the orc brigand.
You can see the orc brigand, the orc scout.
You can't see the orc raider.
But I heard the orc raider because I.
Yeah, you've heard all them all, right?
You said who you can you see.
You know what's going on.
You know, there's like three or four people.
They've hardly been discreet.
Yeah.
I will use my walloping crossbow bolts.
Okay.
They are in partial cover, so just be aware.
So that is a miss.
Okay, then.
Next would be Brigand 2.
Brigand 1.
All right.
I don't know why there's a Brigand one and no Raider 1.
Oh, that should have been a Raider 1.
There is a Raider 1.
Yeah, I got confused in my typing.
It's a Brigand.
Yes, the Brigand.
All right, the Brigand, you know, what does he do?
He moves in to attack the bear.
It seems like the.
Is the sheet not sorted?
We've got a 21 halfway up.
Oh, yeah, it's not sorted.
Oh, you sort after adding the Raiders and shit.
Yeah, it's just that they was just going down this.
So we're sorting at the top of the initiative?
Okay.
Yeah, we're sorting at the top of the initiative.
All right.
Came in late.
The Braider here looks at the.
Okay, so the Brigand, what he does is he will attack the bear.
No!
Actually, the bear is 10 feet up, right?
It's as high up as you said.
The guy had clients.
Yeah, I think that was like 10 feet.
All right.
So he throws a javelin at him.
Her.
Her, Clarity.
Mama Bear.
All right.
Yeah.
Yep.
Sorry.
Let's do.
Yeah, here we go.
Jeez.
He does six points of damage.
Rolling well tonight.
Yes, surprisingly.
Okay.
Who is next?
Raider two and Raider one.
Raider two.
Sort of.
What does he do?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Sees Brewberry.
And throws his javelin at Brewberry and misses entirely.
All right.
Aha.
I catch the javelin as it passes me and I break it in two and growl at him.
Orc Raider two turns to the orc scout.
Orc Raider two screams at orc scout two.
Oh, the orc scout actually screams to orc raider one saying, I told you to not take your brother's uncle, your brother's nephew as a as a as a as a scout.
He was the dumbest scout then and he's the dumbest scout now.
Orc Raider one turns to orc raider two says not the time to have this conversation soon you'll be a dead scout okay all right I think that's it for oh there's one more orc raider orc raider one charges at Brewberry
and attacks Skimatar and hits for six points of damage six points of damage all right
and then he disengages to go over here these he's about to learn the mistake of that action all right do you update the spreadsheet I'll do I update the spreadsheet I sorted it for the top of the initiative and you upgrade your own hit points yeah okay so that's not super consistent yes we call out who's gonna do it it's not you know right vukrid in Europe it's a group effort okay the Indian team support looks like raider two either one of the raiders are both at 37 yeah maybe raider two then
um
range 120 feet all right let's try uh I'm always worried about wisdom saves but let's try wisdom save
You shouldn't be that worried about wisdom saves.
I mean, what they are, after all, orcs.
All right, who are you trying it?
How many?
Raider 2.
He blows it.
So he is charmed.
Okay.
And what is the effect of the charm?
The charm is it must use its action to make a melee attack against a creature that I mentally choose.
So I will tell you at the beginning of its turn who it will be attacking.
Okay, sounds good.
And that is Raider 2.
Yeah, which, oh, and he's up.
So he is charmed.
And let's see.
Who should he attack?
Well, he's upset with the scout.
How many hit points does the scout have?
There's nothing on the tracker.
Oh, there isn't.
Oh, it should be.
30.
It should be 22.
22.
I think I accidentally fat-fingered on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, why don't you go fight the scout?
So, who did you?
Orc Raider 1 or Orc Raider 2?
Raider 2 will be attacking Scout as his action.
Okay.
Did you mark it down?
So I can.
I marked that he's charmed.
All right.
So each round I choose a new target.
Okay.
So fine.
So he charges at Orc Scout 2 and says, Your mother smells of elderberries and your father.
He's almost half a friend.
Your mother was a hamster and your father smells.
All right.
Now go away, unless I taunt you.
Sure, there's an orc insult random generator somewhere on the internet.
That looks like death.
12 points of damage on the orc scout.
He did how much?
12.
So what is down to 10?
What's with the two attacks?
I see 12 and 9.
All right.
Brewberry is up.
No, no, that was the attack die roll.
I'm just using the default damage, which is D6 plus is six points.
So I could avoid spending endless time rolling.
Okay, I just saw multi-attack go-ups.
All right.
So Scout is down to 10 hit points and Brewberry is up.
I'm going to chart with my Halbert at one, of course, is furious at the guy for hitting his brother's nephew and starts screaming at him.
Are you fucking insane?
Like, you know, who do you think you are?
And apparently, this has the potential.
I'm creating a schism in the raiding party that everything is going exactly to plan.
It's appropriate to rage, Stefan.
Rage enlarge, go insane.
All right.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is this?
How do I roll my attack?
That's not what you want to roll.
Oh, it's on the weapon.
Okay.
And then I don't see the roll button.
I don't know how to use this extension.
I'm sorry.
You'll get used to it.
All right.
Got it.
19.
That should be smashing damage.
That should be enough, right?
Seven.
Yes, 19 is a hit.
Right.
And he should be large if he's raging.
I mean, do I want to go into a rage right now?
Always.
Barbarians get huge advantages for raging.
You take less damage when you're raging.
And you do more damage when you're raging.
Yes, but I mean, do we need the extra damage against this whole party of Orcs?
I get three rages before full rest, right?
Yes.
I mean, it's your call.
It's just your call.
It's your call.
You can always rage next round, so it's not the end of the world.
Yes, yes.
No, I won't rage for now.
We'll see how it goes in the next round.
He's a conservative barbarian.
Yeah, that's right.
He likes to lecture me on my morality.
Yeah, dude.
I'm not really enraged.
I just have a little scratch, and I'm actually quite happy that we have this opportunity for Barbecue.
All right.
Fair enough.
Soma, you're up.
Oh, really?
Wasn't there a.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Let's see.
So I guess Brigand is right here in front of me.
He is.
He's on the ground, isn't he?
Yep.
I don't suppose I get any fun advantages for jumping down on his head.
Sure.
Roll an acrobatics check.
Oh, yeah.
I'm fucked.
Or a large 16.
All right, okay.
You managed to jump down on him and roll.
I'd like to shove him a little north if I could.
You want to shove him or knock him prone?
I'd rather shove him a little north.
Like one five-foot square north.
You get advantages on attack.
That's why I'm asking.
Yeah, but if he gets north, I can moonbeam the three of them.
All right.
Okay, so you're going to try to shove him.
Yeah.
All right.
I think my strength can beat that.
So he ends up over there.
You end up down.
Yeah, I'm on the ground, and we're going to moonbeam this circle.
All right.
The orc scout and the orc brigand.
All three of them, yeah.
Orc Raider Scout.
Or Raider 2 brought.
Yeah.
So basically, we're just going to moon.
Oops.
Let me grab the right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can hit them all pretty well.
You're going to moon them.
Gonna moonbeam them.
How big is it?
Is it a five-foot radius?
Five-foot radius, yeah.
Five-foot radius, 40-foot cone, or 40-foot cylinder.
All right, hold on.
That's the wrong circle.
That's close.
There we go.
Yeah.
We can squeeze that there.
Oh, it's snapping, but whatever.
How do I unsnap this?
There we go.
All right.
You want.
Okay, all these guys?
Yeah, I can't.
It's snapping to the grid, but whatever.
Yeah, okay.
I got it.
Yeah, it's going to be there.
Okay.
And so moonbeam.
All right.
Let's see.
Is that it?
Poor radiant damage on all of them?
All right.
Well, I mean, it's sitting there, though, and so they're going to have to deal with it.
More damage?
Yeah, that was on 2d10.
That was a shit roll.
All right.
Orc Raider 2 takes no damage.
Orc Raider, the Orc Scout and the Orc Brigand.
Let me see what they're doing.
It's half damage on a save.
Yeah.
My God, how did I roll that bad?
I don't know.
I know.
I mean, on average, 10.
Believe me, I'm well aware.
This was a waste.
Oh well.
Right.
This is the orcs count.
That's a constitution, right?
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
They did not make their saving throws.
So four, four, and two.
Someone up to.
Can you update that?
Wade.
Yeah, who was the two?
The Raider.
The Raider, Raider Two.
All right, so Raider two gets two.
And then Scout gets four.
And Brigand gets four.
Can we not snap this thing to grid?
Like there we go.
Remove the grid.
No?
Okay.
No, you just need to tell the tool not to snap.
All right.
Okay.
Who's next?
Scout.
With six points.
All right.
The scout has.
Oh, wait, but the orc raider is.
Do you want to fight the raider?
Yeah.
Because, like, he disengages and he uses his longbow on the raider and misses.
Dang.
And then decides to move further away.
All right.
Who's next after that?
Valfina, you're up.
All right.
One, two, three, four, five.
Am I not inside the radius?
You are not inside the radius.
That's your goal.
Okay.
And then I will.
You don't like the light?
It burns.
But it's not sunlight, it's moonlight.
Moonlight is sunlight.
It's inferior light.
It is not directly from the source.
All right.
Four damage on brigand.
It's not fair trade, sunlight.
Sorry.
Four damage on the brigand.
That wasn't lost on everybody.
Wait, don't worry.
Okay.
Next, we have brigand.
Brigand.
All right.
Okay.
The brigand's got a bear.
He's got.
All right.
He's in a really bad position right now.
Back to the pit slave.
He's dealing with the drought dressed as Levander, a bear that casts Moonbeam.
The orc scout who attacked, you know, like he screams, he goes, This was the dumbest idea I had.
And he disengages.
All right.
For our in combat and combat, we are at least, you know, scaring them off.
He disengages.
Like, he's like, I don't want to be dealing with this crap.
Okay, who's up next?
More of you, I believe.
Raider one.
Okay, serious.
Okay, so Raider one is confronted with the problem of orc of Brewberry in front of him and Orc Raider two attacking his brother's nephew.
And he decides that Orc Raider 2 is going to, and he screams at him, you traitor, you whatever, and I'm going to kill this bar, this, this, this creature in front of us, and then I'm going to deal with you, TM.
Bring it on, you orc shrimp.
Who are you calling shrimp?
You.
You smell like one.
He's the brute squad.
I smell like a shrimp.
I don't know what a shrimp smells like, but I'm sure you do.
All right.
He rolls.
He misses with his first attack.
He hits with his second attack.
All right.
And you take five points of damage, six points of damage.
Five or six.
And then six.
Six.
And then he disengages.
And then Brukroton will be next.
Three, four, five.
Six.
All right.
Okay, Vucraden, you're up.
Okay, so do a DC 13 wisdom save to see if you're still charmed.
Ah, he makes he's no longer charmed.
Oh, he made a save?
Yes.
All right.
I rolled very high.
Okay, well, then hang on.
I have to find something else to do.
Hmm.
Hang on.
Do a DC13 intelligence save on Orc Raider 1.
Oh, yeah, he blew it spectacularly.
Okay, so let's see.
Currently to his right is Orc Raider 2.
On his left will appear another image of Orc Raider 2.
So he appears to be surrounded by Orc Raider 2, and that image will attack him and do 9 damage.
He takes 9 damage.
Okay.
So that is what, Raider 1?
Yes.
All right.
So he takes 9 damage.
Believes that he is now surrounded by a clone, a twin or a clone of the guy he was pissed at.
Okay.
But Orc Raider 2 is no longer charmed.
All right.
I have to figure out what I'm going to do next.
He's surrounded.
I'll make that as his condition.
Here's Orc Raider 1.
Attack Orc Raider 2, but can't see Orc Raider 2.
So he was very confused at this point in time.
The Orc 2.
This is the combat of mind games.
What does Orc Raider 2 do?
Geez.
This is where I need all my dice rolling.
All right, so here we go.
What did he do?
There he goes.
When in doubt, attack the Drow.
He screams, what Drow trickery is this?
And rolls a 19 and does six points of damage and then rolls a that's a plus five.
So they're 12 points of damage on Valfina.
12 total or 12 total.
12 total.
Okay.
And screams at the drow that, you know, that it's the drow's fault.
Usually is.
It's fair call.
All right.
Orcs don't trust drow.
Drow, you know, view orcs as food as fit for the slave pens.
That's right.
That's the word I was looking for.
All right.
Who's next?
Is it me?
No, Soma.
No, Brewberry.
Brewberry, you're up.
All right.
I'm going to
go and defend Aldrow.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Just be clear.
Does he get an attack of opportunity when he moves within five when Gary?
When does he get his, like, all of his crazy opportunity things?
For...
So, you know, he's got regular reach.
So Stefan, you can hit him from, say, here.
And I believe...
Let's just double-check because you want to be able to cleave.
No, no, you can't cleave that far.
10 feet.
Yeah.
But anyway, you can hit both of them from here and threaten them if they run away.
Raider one moves without disengaging.
The halberd is 10 feet reach.
Yes.
And Brewberry is like large and all kinds of silliness.
Right.
So this is not large.
This is Halbert.
If you become large, you have a reach of 20 feet.
Yes.
I don't need that reach at the moment, do I?
The advantage you get with the reach, just so you know, is that he also has the ability that if somebody moves within that 20-foot radius, you get an attack of opportunity.
Right.
So maybe just don't go into rage.
Yep.
Right.
We will rage it.
What I like is having them not five feet away and also not at the edge of the reach.
And so if they come in, they get an attack structure.
And if they leave, they get an attack property.
Right, right.
Yeah.
This is a good range for you.
Right.
So you are now raging.
So I'll go attack Raider 2, right?
That's the one that's attacking.
Okay.
Accident.
So with the Halberd.
Roll it.
Oh, Jesus.
What is this?
God damn.
That is a miss, sorry.
All right.
Okay.
Well, I swish my big halberd, and I don't know what I was hacking at, but it wasn't an orc.
All right.
What is it when you take the halberd and you swing it around on top of your head?
Yeah, just screaming at the top of my lungs.
Don't touch my wine.
Yes, they wanted to steal your wine.
All right, who's next?
That would be some, I believe.
Yes.
Yeah, all right.
I give up on this moon beam.
Goodbye.
Stop concentrating.
So I can move up into here.
Right.
All right.
And then we've got Raider one and.
Oh, it's just the two Raiders.
Who's more damage?
We're going to go after Raider.
That is Raider One.
Yeah, this guy.
All right.
And I hate the way that this is making me do rolls on this thing now, but oh well.
Click here to roll.
There's 10 points on Raider 1.
Yep.
Raider 1 goes down to 11.
And then we go ahead and bring on the claws.
Why does it do this?
Yeah.
That looks like a whiff.
All right.
Another whiff.
The scout.
Would have been a lot of damage if I hadn't.
All right.
Okay.
The scout now is confused.
Was Raider 2 really attacking him, or was it the Drow?
Does he, but does he, you know, Orc Raider 1 is screaming, attack orc Raider 2.
Let's make a whiff and check.
What's your spell, DC?
Dave?
10, but who, but why do you ask?
I'm just trying to decide what the scout figures out.
Okay, the scout figures out that, you know, orc raider two and one are hopelessly confused, sees his, and decides that he needs to come back and help his brother's uncles, friend, cousin, whatever.
So he moves to a position and uses his bow against the
and uses his longbow.
Actually, hold on.
He gets an advantage if he moves 15 feet from his original location.
So he moves over here and then he shoots with his long bow and complete and whiffs.
All right.
I rolled a 10.
Okay.
I think it's my turn now.
Yes, I believe so.
Okay.
I will use my crossbow bolts and attack him back, I guess.
The crossbow bolts seem to not be effective today.
Does she blame the introduction of moonlight as the cause?
I suppose.
Okay.
The brigand, however, has decided that he is not dealing with his family trauma and runs away.
Raider one.
What is he going to do?
He thinks he's in a battle with.
Oh, he's attacking Raider two.
He, you know, he's in raid.
The fake raider.
Yeah.
So does he roll?
He's going to least his turn fighting air.
Okay.
Yes.
Orc, the other orc raider two screams at him and says, are you a dummy?
Does he get a saving chance to make a saving throw at the end of his turn?
He has to use his action to study, so he would have to wait until the next round.
Okay.
All right.
So, no, he does nothing this round.
He can take the study action next round, and then he would get another.
I'll have Orc Raider 2 see if he can persuade him.
All right.
I guess I will attack Scout, who has six hit points, huh?
Yes.
I should probably get a little bit closer.
Oh, that's Wade.
What did I just do?
I just moved a giant Wade.
I don't know what happened.
I don't.
Oh, I understand that one.
Okay.
Oh, you moved the little thing in the bottom.
I hate those icons.
You can shrink them, you know, to very small.
Yeah.
Dave, you still attacking the scout.
Okay, and I did not do very well.
Okay.
Despite having a plus five.
That was a very bad die rolling there.
All right.
Not a good roll.
And it is the end of my turn, which means that Raider 1 takes.
Hold on, Raider 1 will take damage.
He takes
13 damage.
And he dies.
Bye-bye, Raider 1.
Right.
And I can stop concentrating on my spell.
Could someone delete the.
I got it.
All right.
Raider two is up.
Okay.
Raider two sees Raider one dead.
Sees the brigand one.
He sees himself surrounded by a giant orc, a giant barbarian, you know, and says, um,
what does he say?
Mom, I think is the word you're looking for.
Yeah.
He decides to try to get in a few whacks on Valfine and then disengage and run away.
All right.
Why?
Because this is a very odd raiding party.
They don't seem very committed to the fight.
The carver has not gotten into their brains.
Maybe they're not part of the Carver's band.
Yeah, maybe not.
Remember, the orcs came down from the mountain as a result of the hold on.
This is what I'm going to keep putting the wrong character sheet.
All right.
So he attacks Valfine 14.
I think that's a miss.
And a 15.
Those are both misses.
All right.
Both of those are misses.
And then he disengages.
The question is: which way does he disengage?
Is he disengaged towards the scout?
He's within my radius for an opportunity attack, isn't he?
No, but he was disengaging.
Ah, okay.
All right.
He disengages and moves that way.
Brewberry.
If you move within five feet, you get an attack of up.
You can attack him.
Well, why not?
I mean, I don't see why I wouldn't do that.
Okay.
Brewberry walks into the forest with like 20 feet.
How tall is he, Dick?
Did we establish 15 feet?
Yeah, I must watch for those branches.
Although, in my rage state, they would just probably scratch me.
Barely notice.
All right, so let me roll this attack here.
God.
13.
That again is a miss.
Oh, wow.
At least I count myself a toothpick out of the branches with my favorite.
Yes, Bruberry now has a toothpick.
All right.
Who's next?
And brings it to me.
All right.
Time for double miss on Raider 2.
Let's go.
All right.
That's critical.
Hey, that's a double miss.
Yeah, you got a critical.
I know, I'm kidding.
Is that 14 damage?
I see.
26.
Yeah, I think that means you bit his butt off.
I mean, only 14, but you know, it's something.
So that takes it down to 21.
I see 20 plus 6.
Oh, 14 damage, yes.
Yeah, 20 plus 6 is just the attack roll.
All right.
Let's finish off the second attack.
The clause.
16 will hit, right?
Yep, it hits.
Another 13.
It's one less than a crit.
All right.
That takes him down to eight.
Guys, I softened him up for you.
Finally, I did my job.
We still got the scout with six hit points, too.
Yeah, scouts harm.
The scout is, everybody hates the scout.
I mean, the scout is like, is like double dashing, you know.
Yeah, we don't.
I don't believe in chasing, you know, down foes.
Yeah, the one time you chased down a foe had what you just did with Raider 2.
A little bit.
He wasn't, yeah, you know.
He didn't fully disengage.
Brewberry likes to point out hypocrisy.
The new Brewberry is the anti-hypocrite.
Oh, believe me, he is the biggest hypocrite.
Oh, he's the.
Yeah, he's bigger than the bear.
He also leaves the combat.
All right.
Alfina, you're up.
Anti-hip.
Okay.
Sorry.
We'll work on that one.
Brueberry, Valfina, you're up.
Yeah, yeah.
So, where did Scout one go?
He left.
He disengaged completely.
Yep, Scotted.
All right.
You can try pursuing him, or you can deal with Raider 2.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Can I see him better from here?
Roll, what's his stealth?
Roll your stealth.
Your perception, rather.
What's your perception?
15.
No.
He manages to sneak away.
All right.
Orc Raider 2.
I couldn't see him.
So then I guess I will shoot Orc Raider 2.
All right.
That's another mess.
The arrows do not like you today.
All right.
The brigand.
Brigand also runs off the board.
So he's like, you know, the family drama has been too much.
Brukadin, you're up.
Are we attacking the Raider?
Are we letting him go?
What's the plan here, guys?
Well, I mean, two already escaped.
What's the point of killing this one?
We killed one and we're letting three run away.
Is that what that's how we're resolving this conflict?
I mean, do you want to tie him up and bring him back to camp with Corbin?
I don't want to be called a hypocrite, so I'm asking Brewberry.
If there's an opportunity for capture, maybe that might be interesting.
I definitely cannot capture anybody.
That is not me.
You're going to have to do that.
That is going to have to be you.
Yeah, I'm the one who's got the gripe with chasing people down.
I can grapple with you.
I mean, I can shoot on range.
I can shoot him if you want.
How many hit points does he have left?
Eight.
Yeah, maybe a little arrow up his butt.
15 hit?
Yes.
No, it misses.
And misses.
He's got 16.
Wow.
16.
That's pretty good AC.
All right.
Brewberry.
No, the Raider's up.
What's he doing?
He has one.
If he runs, what's he doing?
Okay, you get an attack of opportunity, Brewberry.
Did he disengage?
No, he did.
Oh, wait.
He does disengage because he's right next to four.
Yeah, he would disengage.
Yeah, he would disengage because he's right.
Well, he would have.
Yeah, he's his bonus action, right?
So he also then.
No, he can't dash.
So he disengages.
All right, Brewberry, you're up.
All right.
Is there any way that I can capture him if I run within range?
Can I grapple him with something?
Yeah, you can do that.
Totally.
Okay, so let's try to do this.
I'll follow you.
Let's see.
Yeah, your reach.
You have enough reach to grab him.
Yeah, okay.
So I'll try this.
So the way it works is you roll grapple.
Grapple rules and the updated rules changed.
Grapple.
Just doing athletics.
Strength, dexterity.
He chooses which saving throw.
The DC is eight plus my proficiency bonus.
Where is my proficiency bonus on this thing?
Two.
So that's ten plus strength being large as well.
Strength is 17.
No, plus bonus proficiency bonus plus strength.
So that's the bonus strength, right?
Yeah, if you, I think if you use unarmed strike under action, it's the same thing.
So it actually even says it actually even says it.
Yeah, you can just use the unarmed strike.
Yeah, okay.
That's 13.
That's not enough, right?
That's a miss.
Okay.
I guess he gets no, he does not.
Selma, it's Selma's turn.
Selma just waves.
So long, Raider.
The Raider, the Raider.
Okay.
The scout is gone.
Valfina, you're up.
Dave, Gary?
Carrie fell asleep.
There we go.
So we're okay.
So I want to move this way and see if I can see the scout.
Oh, you're really after.
You're really committed to get the scout.
Yeah.
Drows and orcs, man.
They've got the raider over there.
We do.
All right.
So to see, okay, to see the scout, you would have to dash 60 feet into the forest.
Are you doing that?
Sure.
All right.
Roll your perception.
Wait, so if I dash, though, then I can't shoot him.
Yeah, you're chasing each other.
That's my point.
If you can't find it, if you don't.
All right, so you can okay.
So
you can roll, you can want, you can move 30 feet and roll your investigation with a disadvantage, or you can dash and roll it, catch it with 60 feet and roll it normally.
Okay, so I'll do the disadvantage.
All right, he has officially gone out for a one.
Yeah, he is.
The scout has escaped.
Okay.
All right.
Well, we did kill one, guys.
Are we calling it?
We're calling it a day here.
Well, we're capturing Raider 2, right?
We're not capturing him.
He's running away.
Hold on, hold on.
He's like greased up.
All right.
Okay.
However, Creator 2 goes 1, 2.
Hold on.
If he moves, he doesn't disengage because he wants to dash, but because he doesn't disengage, he's within Brewberry's reach, so he would disengage.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
All right.
Brewberry, you're up.
No.
I'm up.
Bukhraden.
Oh, I thought you weren't doing anything.
My bad.
Bukraden, you're up.
I need to do something.
Why don't I try?
Let's see.
If I try.
Sleep.
I have to be within sleep.
How does sleep work?
Range 60 feet.
Is that 45 feet at the moment?
Sure.
We'll put him to sleep.
He gets a slave, though.
Do you see 13?
He blows it.
He is asleep.
There we go.
We wrapped the combat guy.
You can tie him up now.
Yes.
Good.
Orc slave.
Does anybody want to explain to him that we don't do this here in the overbright vukridin, or you're not interfering in epno in different cultures?
He's the one who was charmed, right?
And I got him to attack the scout.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I'll go over and mock him for that.
You mock him?
Absolutely.
Are you using your silvery tongue to mock him, or is this just a general mock?
No, it's just a general mock.
Haunting, really.
He snarls at you.
Corbin shows up a little bit later with some rope and says, so more prisoners?
Yeah.
Who sent you?
Do we have a roster of all the things in camp?
No, no, there's nobody left in camp.
Corbin is in camp.
And we have the.
Other than Corbin the campmaster, right?
So I need to interrogate the orc raider and find out who sent him.
Who sent him?
Is that your question?
Yeah.
He's he snarls at you and growls and rule your intimidation or persuasion.
I'm doing this in orc.
Okay.
He curses.
I mean, I can intimidate him, but I don't speak orc.
Well, I'm sure he speaks common, but.
Yeah, they do speak common.
They do speak common.
Well, I can intimidate him.
I don't get any sort of advantage for doing it in orc.
17 intimidation.
All right.
The orc.
Are you an Asimar?
Is that, if I recall correctly?
No, Celestial.
No, no, you're.
A Celestial is what's your character?
Yeah, I'm an Asimar.
Yes.
All right.
What?
I mean, the orc is very confused.
He's got, you've got an Asimar next to a Drow who's got clearly like religious artifacts related to Lefander.
I mean, he's very, very confused about the situation.
And he's feeling very nervous because, you know, when you combine these kinds, and then the really big looking guy who's now shrank because, you know, the rage ended, he looks at you and says, he says, he goes, nobody, nobody sent us.
We're independent.
We are an independent orc raiding party.
Not anymore.
We were an independent orc raid.
Yeah.
Now you'll barbecue orc.
Hey.
This was, you know, this was not personal.
Ever since we were thrown out of our mountain home up by that dragon, it's been orc.
It's been an orc eat orc world.
Thrown up from where?
What?
You're cannibals?
He looks at you and goes, no, no, it's an explosive.
That's the line from Lord of the Rings.
Guest meets back on the menu, boys.
Which suggests that orcs have a restaurant and a whole civilization around that.
The orc goes
scratches his head and goes.
He pauses, says, you asked from where, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay, so he says, well,
there was a white dragon that.
That was the dragon that attacked us in.
Yeah, so he says there's a dragon in the there was a drag that the orcs, you know, ever since the end of the war, the orcs had occupied the ice spire, the sword mountains.
Finally, the title of the adventure comes into play.
We're working in the sword mountains, and it's, you know, the dragon showed up and kicked them out.
And ever since then, they came down, we came down into the valley, and it's been a free-for-all.
The orc chief, the orc chief, you know, has gone completely crazy.
We've been for it, we've been caught between these Talosian cultists and
cultists, the lotian.
Talos, cult of Talos.
Oh, the Talos cultists.
Yes.
So some of my, some of the members decided after the shaman was killed, some of them decided to join the orc, the orcs of Talos.
Others have decided to join this, this, this, this, this, this, this brigand here.
We decided to be in.
We are orcs and orcs work for orcs.
They don't work for anyone else.
Well, you work for us now.
Oh, no.
Yeah, we've got a cart to pull, orc.
He goes, I just want to be clear.
I just, I don't want to be like unthankful for my life, but do I get paid?
You get paid with your life.
That's how you get paid.
So we killed one orc, right?
Yes.
What do we find on that orc?
What kind of blood money does he have?
Does he have any blood money?
One second.
Do we have any healing potion, by the way?
You have a clear.
We have short rests.
Yes.
You can take a short rest if you wish.
Short rest.
Yes.
I used a prayer of healing to restore everyone.
I guess I can heal the brigand tooth.
Really?
Sure.
Somebody's got to pull the cup, right?
While I drink the wine.
If he has one hit point, he can pull the cart just fine, right?
That's how health works in the D ⁇ D universe.
That's very true.
Doesn't need more than one.
All right.
So you find 15 gold pieces in a mixture of random coins, but we'll just call it 15.
So we'll add that to blood.
I will add that to blood money.
You got it.
Okay, thanks, Gary.
You have enough to open an orphanage or something?
Okay, and the orc needs a name because we can't keep calling him orc number two.
I can.
We'll call him Bruh.
Shrimp.
No, we'll call him Shrimp.
I mean, his name's Robinson.
Shrimp is just fine.
Yep, Shrimpy.
Shrimpy.
Even better.
Just to be clear, my name's Shrimpy.
Trimpy.
No.
Rob.
From now on, and until you pull the cup to the logger's camp, you're shrimpy.
Now shut up and pull the cup.
I'm a little confused about what we're going to do with this guy, but sure, okay.
He's pulling the cart for now.
We can turn him into the authorities at the logger's camp?
No, I mean, haul him back to.
You're going to drag him all the way back to Fandalin?
That's right.
Well, I'm effectively the mayor of Fandalin anyway, so it's not going to happen here.
All right.
Okay.
You want us to let him go?
No, he didn't say that.
Okay.
He definitely did not say.
He's a common criminal stealing treasure from innocent people.
That's right.
So he's going to pull the cup, and once he's done pulling the cup, we'll throw him in jail.
That makes sense.
Right.
Okay.
So.
Alrighty.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
The logging camp spreads along the south shore of the river where a dozen tents are arranged on a sandy beach.
Near a deck stands a cabin with logs stacked under it on awning.
Older cabins close by have been torn down to leave only stone chimneys and foundations.
A grim silence hangs over the camp and you see no one around.
And it is in the morning, or it is 7 in France, so I'm assuming it's in the U.S.
So we will stop here and continue next week.
Wait, we don't see Tiber Wester?
No, you see there's a grim silence which hangs over the camp, and you see no one around.
I brought all these supplies all this way, and I'm not going to get my hundred gold.
Well, you brought the supplies, so strictly speaking.
Yeah, but unless I have a notice of delivery signed by Tiber Wester, I don't get my hundred gold.
I mean, maybe you want to go look forward to it.
Maybe you want to go look for him.
I mean, the real gold is the friends you've made all of them.
To get money, we'll sort it out, Vikridin.
We'll investigate, find out what happened to them, find a guy, and get your notice signed.
All right.
It's just more work than it ought to be, but that's what we'll do.
Yeah, exactly.
It's a lot more.
All right.
Anyway, so I just put you guys on the map so you can see blah, blah, blah.
And so Vukridin and what am I missing?
It's like a battle map.
What?
It looks like a battle map.
Well, it is the map of the camp.
Okay, but as far as we can tell, there's nobody here currently.
Yes, there's nobody here.
And it's , so I just want to be sensitive to people.
All right.
Okay.
This was fun.
By the way, just for the record, is the orc dude tied?
Is he like, how is he kept like, how are you guys tied him to, like, how is it?
He's bound to the cart, right?
Yeah, his hands are tied to the cart's handles, so he can't run away.
Just get him a yoke.
I mean, he could run with a he can run with a cart, but he'll be he could try that, yes.
He wouldn't go very far, though.
We should buy some manacles or something like that.
Brewberry will defend the wine.
Right, right.
Does Valfina explain to Bruberry the correct not tag technique to deal with orc prisoners?
The correct technique is typically to kill them, right?
No, but
well, or sacrifice them to the appropriate in the appropriate ways.
Oh, sacrifice to Lothander.
No, that that that that you recall that that was one of the things that Lothander does not approve of.
He doesn't approve of that, sure.
Yes, he's Lothander.
You know, your training did indicate that that was perhaps something that had to be off the table.
But but but in your news, I have had trading, haven't I?
Yes, you have had trading as a Lothander Priest.
I need to look at this backstory.
No, no, you have had training.
That was part of the backstory.
Okay, all right.
And so, but, but, but, but, you know, as you've started to establish your cult, you realize that sacrifice bad, but in causing pain and healing from pain, not entirely bad.
Well, you know, like there's multiple uses for medicals.
So, like, it's probably useful to have a supply of them anyway.
Yes.
Okay.
All right, guys.
Have a good evening.
Thanks, Cristanis.
Bye.